https://www.dyersonline.com/privacy-policy/

Menu
DepartmentsElectricalGeneratorsGeneratorsGenerator AccessoriesGenerator PartsPower ProtectionSurge GuardsVoltage RegulatorsVoltage MonitorsPower ConvertersPower InvertersInvertersAccessoriesTransfer SwitchesFuse BlocksSolar ProductsPower Cords &
AdaptersExtension CordsAdaptersCord EndsReceptaclesStorage ReelsPower Cord HatchesBatteries & Battery SuppliesBatteriesBatteries Boxes & AccessoriesBattery IsolatorsBattery Cables, Jumpers & ChargersBattery Switches & TestersBattery Watering SystemsSwitches & ReceptaclesSwitchesReceptacles12 Volt PowerLightingFluorescent LightsDome, Reading & Porch LightsDecorative Interior LightingTaillightsClearance/Side Markers & Guide LightsReplacement BulbsReplacement PartsLED Light Bars
PlumbingSinks & DrainsSinksStrainers & PlugsDrains & AdaptersFaucets & Shower FixturesFaucets & DivertersShower Heads & HosesFaucet PartsExterior ShowersAccessoriesShower Wall MountsBathtubs and Shower PansBath TubsShower PansSurroundsShower Doors & CurtainsTub SkirtsShower RepairDrainsFresh Water TanksFresh Water TanksTank FittingsFill HosesDrain CocksFresh Water AccessoriesRV Water PumpsRV Water PumpsWater Pumps Parts & AccessoriesFresh Water ConnectionRegulatorsWater HosesHose AccessoriesWater InletsHeated Water HosesVentsToiletsPermanent Mounted ToiletsPortable ToiletsDometic, Sealand & Thetford Toilet Repair PartsToilet AccessoriesToilet Paper & ChemicalsMacerator ToiletsBlack Water Waste TanksPortable Holding Tanks & AccessoriesPermanent Holding TanksHolding Tank AccessoriesHolding Tank FittingsHolding Tank ChemicalsHolding Tank HeatersWaste Pumps (Macerators)Sewer ConnectionSewer HosesFlushingHose Fittings/AdaptersAccessoriesValvesSewer FittingsRV Water SoftenersWater FiltersWater FiltersReplacement FiltersWater Filter Parts & AccessoriesWinterizingBlow-Out PlugsBy-Pass KitsPlumbing FittingsElbowsTeesConnectorsCapsValvesTubing, Clips & Parts
HardwareExteriorInsert TrimRV Gutter SystemsSlide-Out
HardwareRoof Vents, Portable & Ceiling FansRoof VentsRoof Vent CoversRoof Vent GarnishesRoof Vent Replacement PartsRoof Vent AccessoriesCeiling FansPortable FansDometic Heki Sky LightsExit Roof VentsSkylightsSkylight - OuterInner GarnishEntry DoorRV Entrance DoorsStepsWindow FramesGrab HandlesScreen
DoorLocks and Lock PartsHoldbacks & BumpersAccessoriesRV Fender Flares/SkirtsSingle Axle Fender SkirtsTandem Axle Fender SkirtsTriple Axle Fender SkirtsInterior DoorFolding DoorsLatchesRollers & GuidesMiscellaneous Interior Door HardwareSlide-Out PartsAwningsComplete AwningsAwning Parts & AccessoriesWindow PartsOperatorsKnobs & CranksPartsWindow SealsWindow CoveringsScreens, Shades & Sun ProtectorsDrapes & CurtainsCurtain HardwareTracksMiscellaneous Window HardwareHatch & CompartmentsBaggage Doors & SlidesCable HatchesCatchesLatchesCam LocksMiscellaneous Hatch & CompartmentKeys & Key BlanksTableSupports & BracketsLegs & BasesCabinet & DrawerLatches & CatchesHinges & SupportsKnobs & PullsSlides & SocketsBunk Clamps & LocksShelf SupportMiscellaneous Cabinet & DrawerGas PropsGas PropsBrackets & StudsFasteners
RV AppliancesRefrigeratorsRefrigeratorsIce Chests and Portable Refrigerators/FreezersIce MakersRefrigerator PartsRefrigerator AccessoriesRefrigerator Door PanelsMicrowavesOver the RangeCountertopBuilt-InRanges & CooktopsRangesCooktopsCoversHoods & VentsRange, Hood & Vent PartsRange & Cooktop AccessoriesRange & Cooktop PartsDishwashersCoffee MakersWashers & DryersWashersDryersWasher/Dryer CombosVents, Pans & Stack KitsLaundry AccessoriesWasher & Dryer Repair PartsVacuum SystemsVacuum SystemsAttachment Kits & AccessoriesAir ConditionersAir ConditionersAir Conditioner Repair PartsRV Water HeatersRV Water HeatersWater Heater DoorsParts & AccessoriesFurnacesFurnacesPortable HeatersParts & AccessoriesFireplacesLP GasCarbon Monoxide, LP, & Smoke DetectorsRegulators & ChangeoversLP KitsTees & FittingsHoses & PigtailsTanks & Tank AcessoriesCircuit Boards
Jacks & LevelersTongue JacksTruck Camper JacksStabilizer & Leveling JacksTripodScissor "C" Series"T" TypeTelescopingOtherStabilizer BarsLanding GearSlide Out SupportsWheel Chocks & Jack StandsJack Pads & Leveling BlocksSkid WheelsLevelsFoot Pads, Casters & PartsPop Camper Power Lift System
ElectronicsRV Satellite SystemsAntennasReceiversInternet & GadgetsTV'sSatellite & Antenna Parts & AccessoriesReceptacles & TV AccessoriesSpeakers
Towing & AutomotiveHitchesWeight Distribution Hitches5th Wheel HitchesGooseneck HitchesReceiver HitchesBall Mount HitchesPintle Hooks, Lunette Rings, Hitch BallsHitch Adapters & Pin BoxesHitch Parts & AccessoriesTow Bars & BaseplatesTow BarsVehicle Base PlatesTow Bar Wiring & AccessoriesTrailer Wiring & AdaptersTrailer AdaptersTrailer WiringCarriers, Tie Downs & Trailer OrganizationMotorcycle, Bike, Cargo & Tire CarriersTrailer Tie Downs & OrganizationTruck Camper Tie DownsTow Car Windshield ProtectorsBraking SystemsBrake ControllersTow Vehicle Braking UnitsMobile Home Brake AssembliesBrake AssembliesTrailer Surge Brake ActuatorsSteering, Suspension, and Trac BarsTracBars and Steering Upgrades5th Wheel, Travel Trailer, & Utility Trailer Suspension ComponentsBlue Ox Sway & Trak BarsTire Pressure MonitorsBack-Up Cameras & SensorsMirrorsSun Visors & ProtectionTruck & Auto AccessoriesTonneau CoversTruck Cargo Management & Steps5th Wheel TailgatesInflatable MattressesAir Bag & Suspension SystemsGauges, Compasses & GPSSplash Stops, Stone Guards, Mud Flaps & Exhaust TurndownsAuto DecalsMaintenance & Emergency Equipment Wind DeflectorsTruck Lighting & Exterior AccessoriesTruck Exhaust and Intake SystemsSnow Plows, Salt Spreaders, and Replacement PartsJeep & Truck BumpersAir HornsValve ExtendersTow DolliesKar Kaddy & Tow DolliesParts & AccessoriesTow Light KitsTrailer Movers
RV & Trailer CareRV, Motorhome, Trailer, Camper, Horse Trailer,
& Tire CoversClass A CoversClass C Covers5th Wheel & Toy Hauler CoversToy Hauler & Travel Trailer CoversPop-Up Trailer CoversHi-Lo Trailer CoversTruck Camper CoversR-Pod CoversSpare Tire CoversTyre GardsTruck CoversHorse Trailer CoversRV Roof CoversStorage Lot RV CoversSpot Removers & WaxesMoisture & Odor AbsorbersRubber Roof ReplacementsRoof Repair & CoatingRoof Care & SealantsRepair KitsLubricants & ProtectantsSeals, Tapes & AdhesivesTrailer Repair PartsU-BoltsAxle PartsSurge Brake Actuator PartsPintle Hooks, Pins, & ClipsLeaf SpringsTires and WheelsTrailer HubsBoat Trailer PartsTrailer Axles & SpindlesCouplersWinchesWinch Replacement PartsTrailer FendersTrailer Brake Assemblies
RV LifestyleOutdoor LivingSteps, Ladders & Flag PolesRV Step RugsPatio MatsStorage - Containers, Straps & HooksGrills & AccessoriesCampfirePicnic Supplies, Ice Chests, & Insect ControlChairs5th Wheel SkirtsAwnings Rooms, Screens & ExtensionsAwning SystemsAwning, Patio Lights & Track AccessoriesBicyclesOverlandingTablesIndoor LivingBooks, Games & ToysFasteners & OrganizersBrooms & Waste BasketsKitchen AccessoriesBeddingPet ProductsPest ControlIndoor AccessoriesRV FurnitureRV FireplacesRV FlooringRV ClothingRV Starter Kits
CLEARANCE SALE!BrandsFAQContact UsCompare
Compare Products
Remove This Item
Compare
Clear All
You have no items to compare.
Account
Flat rate shipping
$9.98 ground shipping
Phone support
Fast, professional customer service
Extended return period
30 days return policy
Fast Shipping
Most in stock orders arrive 2-5 business days!
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Dyer's uses and protects any information that you give Dyer's when you use this website. Dyer's is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Dyer's may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
Introduction
This privacy policy is here to inform our customer's how we use any and all personal information collected at this site.
Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information.
By using this site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.
These
practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis.
You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to
make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only.
If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Please see below under "Links to Other Websites"
Links to Other Websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest.
However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
What We Collect
We collect personally identifiable information such as; names, postal addresses, physical addresses, company names, company addresses, email addresses, phone numbers, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors.
We may also collect demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests as well as other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.
The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided unless requested not to receive those promotions and/or updates.
What We Do With the Information We Gather
The site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customize the website for visitors.
Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and/or other tracking technology, however, if you have previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.
Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
- Internal record keeping
- We may use this information to improve our products and services
- We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information we think you may find
interesting using the email address which you have provided.
- From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you via email for market research purposes.
We may use the
information to customize the website according to your interests.
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation.
We may do so when: (1)
permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place.
The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
How We Use Cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site.
Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual.
The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used.
This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs.
We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not.
A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.
This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of Cookies We Collect section.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure.
In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure.
Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.
All emails and newsletters from this site, except for order confirmation, order update, order tracking and/or review emails, allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Controlling Your Personal Information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
- Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the
information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
- Check out as a "Guest" so that your information is used to register for an account on the website
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to us or email us at support@dyersonline.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 4122 W Innovative Dr STE 105 Phoenix, AZ 85086.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us by visiting the contact page below:
Contact Us
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy.
Any changes to this policy will be posted.
List of Cookies We Collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE name
COOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
You have no items in your wish list.
Waste Pumps (Macerators)
5th Wheel, Travel Trailer, & Utility Trailer Suspension Components
RV, Motorhome, Trailer, Camper, Horse Trailer,
CLEARANCE SALE!
